>> Jem Young: 在安全方面，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: When it comes to security,
我们思考如何锁定我们的服务器有几个关键的方法。
there are a few key ways that we think
about how to lock down our server.
我们之前谈到的第一个是 SSH，安全的插座外壳。
The first one we talked about before
was SSH, secure socket shell.
因此，我们不使用用户名和密码，而是使用 SSH。
So instead of using a username and
password, we use SSH.
因为用户名密码的问题是，一个，人类，
Because the problem with a username
password is, one, humans,
我们会反复重复使用相同的密码。
we tend to reuse the same
password over and over again.
或者，我们将使用密码或密码 1 的变体。
Or we'll use variations of password or
password1.
事实上，安全研究人员，当他们看到被盗的密码时，他们说，
In fact, security researchers, when
they look at stolen passwords, they say,
最常用的五个常用密码是什么 ?
what are the top five
common stolen passwords?
他们就像 12345
And they're like 12345.
你就像我把密码要求八个字
And you're like, I made my password
requirement eight characters
而不是五个更安全的人
rather than five cuz that's more secure.
那么人们是做什么的呢 ?
So what do people do?
12345678 .
12345678.
我没开玩笑，如果你看黑密码，会是密码或者
I'm not kidding, if you look at hacked
passwords, it'll be password or
与 @ 符号相反的密码。
password with,
instead of an a, an @ symbol.
人类我们是自己最糟糕的敌人
Humans, we're our own worst enemy.
我们所做的就是建立这些安全规则
So what we do is we create
these security rules and
帮助我们不要用脚射中自己的协议
protocols that help us kind of not shoot
ourselves in our foot, cuz you will.
如果我没告诉你我们可能还会以根为根
If I didn't tell you, we'd probably
still be doing everything as root, and
糟糕的事情就会发生
bad things entail.
因此，最好遵循社区的最佳实践。
So it's best to follow the best
practices of the community.
另一种处理安全性的方法，以及
Another way of handling security, and
你可能都熟悉的就是防火墙
the one you're probably all familiar with,
is firewalls.
另一个就是把你的软件保持在最新的状态。
Another one is just keeping
your software just up-to-date.
因为漏洞和零天，它们一直在发生。
Because vulnerabilities and
zero days, they happen all the time.
其实零天就有很大的钱。
In fact, there is big money in zero days.
我说零天，但是什么是零日呢 ?
And I say zero days,
but what is a zero day?
我肯定你以前听过这个词
I'm sure you've heard the term before.
>> 扬声器 2: 未修补的漏洞。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Unpatched vulnerability.
>> Jem Young: 这是一个毫无漏洞的漏洞，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's
an unpatched vulnerability,
尤其是公司本身，所以微软或者
specifically one that the company itself,
so Microsoft or
Apple 或 Google 尚未找到或记录。
Apple or Google,
has not found or documented yet.
所以它是一个无证件的弱势，零天的价值是一吨的钱。
So it's an undocumented vulnerability,
and zero days are worth a ton of money.
我们说的是百万美元取决于利用的是什么
We're talking millions of dollars,
depending on what the exploit is.
还有那么多的公司
And there's so much so
that there's entire companies
他们所做的就是试着寻找零天然后把它们卖给出价最高的人
that all they do is try to find zero days
and then sell them to the highest bidders.
这些都是世界上的灰色帽子因为他们就像
These are kind of known as gray hats
in the world, because they're like,
这事我们没做任何坏事
well, we're not actually
doing anything bad with this.
我们只是把它交给别人
We're just handing it off to someone else.
所以，灰色帽子被称为一个道德模棱两可的人。
So gray hat is known as someone
who's morally ambiguous.
好的安全研究人员试图保护你和
The good security researchers, the people
that are trying to protect you and
使您的软件保持最新，并尝试查找漏洞和
keep your software up-to-date and
are trying to find vulnerabilities and
然后告诉公司他们被称为白帽子黑客，
then tell the companies about them
are known as white hat hackers,
而且是保安人员
and are security people.
而那些坏的，滑稽的，都被称为黑帽。
And the bad ones, the nefarious ones,
are known as black hats.
然后这里是黑客和坏人的最低级别
And then there's the lowest here of
hackers and bad security people,
被称为剧本基子
which are known as script kiddies.
那些只是从互联网下载东西的人
Those are people that just download
things from the Internet and
然后针对整个 IP 范围运行它以尝试中断，是吗 ?
then run it against entire IP
ranges trying to break in, yes?
>> 演讲者 3: 最着名的零天事物之一是 Stuxnet，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: One of the most
famous zero day things was Stuxnet,
我们的政府或者袭击伊朗的人
where our government or
whoever attacked the Iran
放射性程序什么的核计划
radioactive program or
whatever, nuclear program.
然后他们用了四天零的时间
And then they used four zero day things
把这蠕虫传播到
as a worm to spread this worm into
这设施简直太疯狂了
the facility, it's just crazy.
>> Jem Young: Stuxnet 是迷人的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Stuxnet is fascinating.
我们说的是安全每个政府都有自己的
We're talking about security, every
government in the world has their own
安全团队和黑客团队以及零日团队
security teams and
hacking teams and zero day teams.
他们说的不多但是
They won't talk much about it, but
他们都有他们因为这场网络战已经开始了
they all have them because it's
this cyber war that's going on.
但我不会说战争的但这不是官方的
But I won't say war,
cuz it's not official, but
每个人都在试图闯进所有人
pretty much everybody's trying to
break into everybody all the time.
如果您查看您的认证日志，您将看到有人尝试在您的
If you look at your auth log you see that
there's people trying to break in your
就在服务器上
server right now.
Stuxnet 是一个非常有趣的例子。
Stuxnet is a really interesting example.
如果他们能进入你的服务器，他们能做些什么呢 ?
And it goes back to, what can someone
do if they gain access to your server?
所以 Stuxnet 做的是把一堆零日链在一起
So what Stuxnet did was they
chained a bunch of zero day, so
都是未经修补的未知的虫子
that is unpatched, unknown bugs.
它们通常以堆溢出或类似的方式开始。
And they usually start with some sort of
a stack overflow or something like that,
一些无害的东西
something innocuous.
但如果你能让电脑栈溢出的话，你就可以把它丢出一个错误，
But if you can make a computer stack
overflow, you can make it throw an error,
这个错误你可以控制
and that error, you can control.
一旦你开始把这些人联系起来
And then once you start
chaining those together,
你可以开始做点什么
you can actually start doing something.
所以即使是最轻微的脆弱性，如果有人知道，
So even the most minor vulnerability can
turn into something major if someone knows
他们在做什么
what they're doing.
Stuxnet 做的是把软件植入
And what Stuxnet did was
they planted software into,
我想说它是 USB 驱动器，就是这样开始的。
I wanna say it was the USB drives,
that's how it started.
因为这是提炼浓缩铀或钚的核设施，
Because this was a nuclear facility
that refined uranium, or plutonium,
可能是铀
probably uranium.
他们就像是
And they're like, okay,
我们知道我们正在处理非常危险的事情
we know we're dealing with things
that are really dangerous.
我们根本不可能连接到互联网。
We're not gonna connect
to the Internet at all.
Stuxnet 做了什么，他们把它连在了一个人的 USB 驱动器上。
So what Stuxnet did was they
hooked up to someone's USB drive.
所以我不知道，一个秘书或一个人，每当他们侵入他们的电脑时。
So I don't know, a secretary or someone,
so whenever they hacked their computer.
所以当他们插进 USB 驱动器的时候，他们就把软件扔进了那个。
So whenever they plugged in the USB drive,
they dumped the software into that.
所以当那个人去工作的时候，他们插上了那个 U 盘，
So when that person went to work and
they plugged in that USB to,
我不知道，看电影什么的，核设施里的人怎么做，
I don't know, watch movies or something,
whatever people at nuclear facilities do,
在他们的服务器上
that now got on to their server.
所以即使那台电脑还没有连接到互联网上
So even though that computer wasn't
connected at all to the Internet, they now
成功地渗透到整个网络，而这就是下一个级别的黑客攻击。
managed to infiltrate the entire network,
which honestly is next level hacking.
如果你可以黑进某人的服务器而不与它连接
If you can hack someone's server
without actually being connected to it,
就好像只有政府能做到或者真的
that's like only something governments
can achieve, or really, really,
真正的大公司
really big funded companies.
但他们做的真的很微妙。
But what they did was really subtle.
他们只是关闭了提炼浓缩铀的东西。
They just turned off the controls for
the things that refined uranium.
所以他们让他们失控了
So they just made them
spin out of control.
他们摧毁了数百万美元的机器和机器
And they literally destroyed millions and
millions of dollars in machinery and
让他们重新回到过去
set them back years.
因为他们的服务器不安全，安全协议很糟糕。
All because their servers weren't secure
and their security protocols were bad.
所以，我再一次说，这是为了吓唬你，因为你应该害怕。
So again, I say this to scare you
because you should be scared.
你不知道安全性差的意外后果。
You don't know the unintended
consequences of having bad security.
另一个常见的安全因子是两个因子认证。
Another common security factor
is two factor authentication.
这就意味着你会用 SSH 的方式
That just means instead of just SSHing,
you would SSH and
他们就会向你的手机发送某种推送通知
then they send some sort of push
notification to your phone.
你会把你的电话或 UB 的钥匙插在你的手机里然后你说
A device you'd have on you or a UB key you
plug into your phone, and then you say,
对我就是这个
yes, this is me.
这是另一个我们都很熟悉的认证层。
It's just another layer of authentication
that we're all pretty familiar with.
但这并不总是可行的，因为周围有各种方法。
But that doesn't always work too
because there are ways around that.
例如， Twitter 的 CEO Jack Dorsey 被黑客侵入
For instance, Jack Dorsey, CEO of Twitter,
got hacked because Twitter
有这个奇怪的变通方法你可以通过短信发送推文
has this weird workaround where you can
still send tweets via text message.
他们做的都是叫电话电报电话他们说
So all they did was they called
up AT&amp;T and they said, or
不管他的电话公司是什么，他们说，嘿，我有个新电话，我是杰克 - 多尔西。
whatever his phone company was, they said,
hey, I got a new phone, I'm Jack Dorsey.
他们就像你确定吗
And they're like, are you sure?
他们就像是
They're like, yeah.
他们就像好吧听起来不错
They're like, okay, sounds good to me.
所以他的密码很可能是他的两个因子认证
And so his probably long password,
his two factor authentication was rendered
一文不值因为只有一种方法
worthless because there's
just a way around it.
这就是为什么当我们想到安全的时候
That's why when we think about security
we're talking about creating an entire
我们所做的一切
wall around everything we do.
然后我们说的每一步你确定吗
And then every step of the way we say,
are you sure?
你确定吗 而且
Are you sure?
And
当我们有 sudo 的东西时，它看起来很麻烦，但这是因为它。
it seems really onerous whenever we have
the sudo things, but it's because of that.
您总是希望在方式的每个步骤上都有安全性。
You always want security
on every step of the way.
可能大多数公司使用的另一个安全功能是 VPN，
Another security feature that
probably most companies use is a VPN,
虚拟专用网。
a virtual private network.
那就是网络和网络之间的墙
That's essentially a wall
between the Internet and
我们之前讨论过的内联网
the Intranet, which we discussed earlier.
内部网是私人互联网。
Intranet is private Internet.
这就意味着所有穿过墙的东西都是未支配的。
And it just means everything
through the wall is unencumbered.
你可以发展，你可以推动，你可以拉，
You can develop,
you can push, you can pull,
只要通过 VPN 的严格程度，就可以登录到服务器。
you can login to servers as long as
you pass through the rigor of the VPN.
>> Jem Young: 我可以晚点再谈 VPN ，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I can talk more
about VPNs a little later,
他们现在也不是很关键
cuz they're not super critical right now.
但总的来说，我使用 VPN 冲浪。
But in general,
I surf the Internet using a VPN.
也许你应该在某个时候
Probably most of you should at some point.
更安全一点也能防止偷窥
It's a little safer and
it prevents snooping.
>> Jem Young: 我稍后会说，如果你想，到最后。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'll talk about that later,
if you want, towards the end.
我不想挂在保安上
I don't wanna get hung up on security,
我一直在讲关于它的故事很有趣
cuz I keep telling stories about
it cuz they're really interesting.